At Trilles AI, we worked with a lot of engineers, but I just wanted to give a huge shout out to Daniyal Aziz.
The work that he did was exceptional.
He worked with us on different projects across different clients,
but I just wanted to mention a few of the projects he did with us.
The lead intake system, the Pinterest automation, the eBay automation, and the Dutch voice AI agent that he made.
And most importantly, the database creation for an e-commerce business was exceptional.
And Daniyal is not just about building code.
I see the systems thinking, the system design thinking in him as well.
So if you are building a great AI product or something like that,
Daniyal would be the best fit for it, and I would highly, highly recommend him for any kind of AI build.
Thank you.